{
  "LANGHINDI": 18,
  "qu1": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tLinear Discriminant Analysis (LDA) is a dimensionality reduction technique that</p>",
      "OPT1": "Maximize the variance in the original features.",
      "OPT2": "Minimize the correlation between features.",
      "OPT3": "Create new feature that are linear combinations of the original features.",
      "OPT4": "Maximizes the separability between different class.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu2": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhat does the assumption of linearity in linear regression imply?</p>",
      "OPT1": "The relationship between the independent and dependent variables is non-linear.",
      "OPT2": "The residuals exhibit a constant variance.",
      "OPT3": "The relationship between the independent and dependent variables can be represented by a straight line.",
      "OPT4": "The residuals are normally distributed.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu3": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following may help to reduce underfitting demonstrated by a model.<br />\r\n\t<em>S</em><sub>1</sub> : Increase model complexity.<br />\r\n\t<em>S</em><sub>2</sub> : Increase the number of optimization routine step.</p>",
      "OPT1": "<p>\r\n\tOnly <em>S</em><sub>1</sub></p>",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\tBoth <em>S</em><sub>1</sub> and <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "OPT3": "<p>\r\n\tOnly <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "OPT4": "<p>\r\n\tNeither <em>S</em><sub>1</sub> nor <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu4": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tConsider a simple linear regression model <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAO8AAAAfCAYAAAAP4pqgAAALGklEQVR4Xu1be1QU1x3+YnJyPMRYiWiIVtskELTm+Fg1JZFGgujxgQooWhEEDRIUZFmooFEQRDwiEVDwRTa6RJRAFNHgM2iRQouas0maqseitYQeSqwPRKqJNdg7d+4s+5jZBVnRdWf9i925c+/v+/2+3+Ob8ZkH5AP5IyMgI2BzCDwjk9fmfCYfWEaAIiCTVw4EGQEbRUAmr406Tj62jIBMXjkGZARsFAGZvDbqOPnYMgIyeR9HDLQ2QnvoFCoPVMAxIQshrt0fxynkPQUEqD8OY7/mv/ArWgLFc7YBjUzervZTYynC3VU4Sfedig01mZjubCPRYlWsWtFSewLq9CTkljfSOzt4xyI7IQRerj2tupO5m93XZsHdfxOauIsco1F8VvV4yNtSi5Mfr0fMxnLc4c4yeC6S06IQqHBGNwkDZPJ2WZjob3QNFStnIKxgmP2St/Ui8v0+xBVVDpI8+wGNJ7B6fjQK6iZgQ3k6pvd7vus8c1+L7NEzkIvHRd4fUatRIaN5HlZHvY2+V9uHxVNM3vtoLI2FR5kXqtS+cO66UGjHTi3QZs3CrI0u9kve5gokJjQhcqvgm1Y0V6TAI/QLuGcfRJ7vL9uBo5UuEcg7cBWO7A+Fq1Sps9J2prf5Fw4syscv0pfDsye3OUfmMExKvoGokmLEKHqI7kzJ29qoxeGjJdiafBj99YBrrdVgxvhy+H6ptspc1raPFuO5Qw0nQbw7F4mJf4JCsw+pns+j9kQ+MpbsBNbyDmxtKEWUtwrH4ctnZOcb+Co3EQu29cOmmlXMWDHbHoa8zWz/TJwkvYtD0E5UrfGE9Zu4J4i8wry3ZQOOTNiFGtWbuKbdi80r0nBg5GZi/7voJrS3SHikiZBvYXdB8bjIOzLLgn1dFR+MvEW/RfHnkVD0EM8mhLx3H9Tu2oijLm74afFq/H2VkPXYDfZ7i2QjkinCpiGu/KZELhoskjFIq5ilwa0RL+FQ6EmMKVHi2VPnMCjADVVTU4G8LAz/SzlujR+EK4GrcT2LIzNQqanEy/6DURM8F6V+GuT0Po2KN/zgffcHYOgQOEtmyQ6St+Uc8mOWotojA5mhQ+BAEldQ2VB8qlJAfCJl94/5og0DYWa6Q6pK8Hfw280Bf4dV2Qv8dd5cgHijgVXejJLJ+HZFHAoucNnCG1E58Qgb5wqaazliHSzEtg830WTC/a7MT0XkaG4OIoFUcQyHCo4DPu/h+vY0FNbNhJpLaD2umlmn7zKu2m1FZtPreLUsBaUe2Vj77Bn8cdBEvFWlRAQSUTrib9jbNBzDr6xC9PV4kWQmgoNRVPRS7iNJQQpH4WKh8l5GnFSxIHNhxV6S3JN346LJXHgPjdpyHCvZhWqXEEy5tBVxBX8lVznDS7kaSxeOg6tAAiNcHd7zxqjT5ah8xwx52xsfBpqGCD0sztVEC7i4B7HxdQjcvhSeztLjQ1vbTFuHMJwXyEtnkjmEMIXYF+omOTR3tJPgs2spBgQtxrplAXBrOUgEnDwgaBoCoxbA0+HPSHQvwaiT+kIOSyS7f0ZQdDqSpg4UP4/Q/kjlFIglFc6Ce2goTcDEncOwT2ibWv4B7b+doDArnhCgtZsx2z8T9boqLbQ89ZhDuwkncn8+wCcc88LRzb7o102ovDfhFZtpNOcIBCQJMnI24v7pA/VOzok/4qImAQHJV7GgKAKICEcutdMBbkoNihYC6pAavFs4HfVKiXUln5AWrJepyyhuwTgy0A/B6+MR5NZMknMA8jAOE4mfIklHVLlyHvaMynt07Wzr98TeYOS98RGKVKP55GXw4TBLwXc+qXwX2HIW2QGhyG0MIyJTAOoj2oqJg3cCdqxZgFF9ScFIWYSw/KY2X9B1H+DLkUnIXjYNrg4k0dHujyQEmljFRqyHjY+OsYPvdImNwjILopUReVWs4jnB2i0zfx4hS99AIsuuApknsUCnf6c4otBo9uCvu4LEdquzHai8nUlUdK0/Ur/ngogolVzVHZsGrVMD6l3SeLKCBKaSJKjlSUyIEWubDUWsqbcLiCM3oY9+C0mz+gr8J7mEJNRf4bLIXMT7zdw6kURscF/yO0uCO6awsYH+nQnHYuuMT6YhzZNjWtlI7M4OhJtEmwjabZzC+RuXcGgl60Z0ij3pRURmZsNW3InNktDFHx+WTLCSaps7Ex8d4y+7mlPiDyI9egUKL4wwPKve/drIywkI7uvRu4AbkO+TLPc+Zn3qISGdP0zbzO3KB22orv1iBNupYK05X7VmXAozas+ECleL8EdBXgPbxcUBaR8IlZYLiFy8U61CPPmn+fVn+F0o3wIGYy+iytywXldRxMhr+N2Uhpy2RxhGm/Nt6FBc4wS5mEsGI4rBow/RdabtK10T1ISPBA2BknkvxrAESxPC9CtQimoMnW2bed8Gb3HEOnPEpZWZdBRH+mJO8nyMG/MWepaFGYh+YjOz4XfdeZX/kK9hXFsib0fio9Nts+A0y6JVG3nppnn4DRGSop3LqUhU5W9lwYZmsFBUz/+ctV98tflD7yx+JqK/R+GSqpC1m8wQ0urkrNmBrw+eR/8tQitqKaV1oPLq2S6l7Jnbja92GYAyBmPO3YNX9iIoWitJMoyEduE6hDd9BXywQu/xh2Xy8pWX3JNWWbGxRSCNIXl1Z5FcZ2wJC5KqmaxlZLOnqhc09JmnVEK1hH97fufnu/hsAl2GuYpLxn8BY51dphhaJm8vpj+81LHK28n4sIgESQ7JG4DYFH1xlNl3fJKkaGVKXk0inL4ux7njlXguwYhEFk9h4QKawdRwOcDaL+M5m/3+2pbZqCv/GXNDXsHtF/qiWV2MW2QGQ9Jc5A3JxieTL2PbmZFICrbSLE735YhGZkeuOlIF9htgtBcUfW/wM9Gel5EqpfzpqgIwIbsIub7cTC5kzmoR1VrsOa/w3QA+sF6/yleaU2+2iVT653K+xwIRhuKgcBbJdcYCCLfvHGx0yWVJggXNuXBGZvb7a/FYUncGtxclWOmlEiIwnd2BpDX/QwQV9sw/nxHIe4+b71XDyMhL1oakEyFPeNHFXNusxgBKelfcETQK3VzMnl5kkpcjhkk8KjIXH2YEpXbThRatcFSPW0f1D+duDJvwbzHms3SEuPUUSV76/yWQHnA5fli4GnFj67EsqE6iTWr3kYwuZBl9MXSPeHiHFGMse5bF/70dfZSxCPQZi/7VsZi0/kUk7ucM6M6LSjE1cFcmIGLOZCisARw9ZTMTg47St1scvKOREuSD8Z6uVHXmzvSKjpRi9pvaxl0lqhuYtFWOpFJzCj/0FHz2nfddk7duEskbSDM8bkPNvVSgJ8wZKLoib+vQdcQek6GA+n0VIHQ0bIbP8eQeGwndkD829AnTYdLRwcIUsTahj6rGJh+RN89aG5j4RBRkqrrH422iiP9+I1Pxje9BxScfgI4W7IkA/W4yoCM+WTQ4DOqPvfDN1ECGp5ioKR0fnceCOzgha0UG3g9V8yo6VcgNY1ysoxJ5SYOrGIsQc3OxhOr3sOS1xXWsZTw9k6nEtmiDfOanFQFT8nJS+txivLo1rWtfUXsCEeZeEFGltmCxhXnsCTy6fCQ7QICQ99aDi5qVWIlIFM17EZUp8SgesZbNbXaAgGyijICNIkDI+9MDfpYsxR2DN3hs1CL52DICdoLAU/wfE+zEg7KZdouATF67db1suK0jIJPX1j0on99uEZDJa7eulw23dQRk8tq6B+Xz2y0CMnnt1vWy4baOgExeW/egfH67RUAmr926Xjbc1hGQyWvrHpTPb7cI/B/MTcz+5YplJAAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" /> What is the predicted value of y when <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAADMAAAAkCAYAAAAkcgIJAAAC+UlEQVRYR+2VfUhTYRTGn1lEmIwigiF9ILVGUmELQVJrLSKF0LlI8yO2sA9iyzbFRuicYWZSsaWZWDMbgYapbIugkQwFMWEwYSRRUX9EiET2xZAS27rXOVtLudc775C49+/33PP8nuec9+X5iQ//ycfjYJZoklwySzQYcMlwyUTBgeiO2ZQbpuQjuPUljGxNCTpdWoiXT2LMdQ9Vino4J8gzO5FfUwlVYTIEMdRuRB8m3YYkhwES/hzqfK9gUVmxyaCFRLAC+N4HfYoKLy70oFspAhVP9GGk/djrJFOgdhrBJHcbMWCWQUBRQsD89I9adcjQWIFMI542EUUfn6OpshR3BXUYuCwBn0ZfWkdIcQuBmU7mBGzyNlo6eP5vg36LjY+cFBcUB3shc+ix1uGBUJmKH+9isCNJEBbvFMaspUjTPJ5X/+rz3RjSivGP+SRMeiPG931Gx0NPoH5bIapr1SgQh/eZxLTJLXzUNJQhW0ht6Z8xI+c1Jx/tyMG5Zh0OxxMzu9gfCZNnQ8JVUlwcvG/sqC+pQMfLXdA/M0MhXDnT0QevuxXX3x9ClWwj5a4EZYbsjBduYy5yR07Tms/F4fQRO34JacoubK4OWXKvC6aj7Uhou4ZsAZ3lCqgJgflKwBQTMMcpYCIYszkcmHIbkSI3Y8MsTABQ2rsfzgXu6wxMINba2048GdyKhqF5rs6I4viEPqMd/FNKiOOCl2wwmbcoCxkz36gV2jpAd1OGeKr7OEQT73X/sH/VlnG0tkyg+MwvVO95gMQeIzI9nXClqlE0O8cRkRDF5EJXQDWcgWbDAeIRJB5IdxeaKrqxTNeIKkk87d2YTwnvflai/8a6i3hkKoAo9gNsqjyU9W+H+spZHMsS03p5aWN6R2DRnERN7xhREgtRUTnKFXJI/rqpgmM8AKnJjjuy9bR/H91Hk7YsZgc5GGa+sV/FJcO+x8w6cMkw8439Ki4Z9j1m1oFLhplv7FdxybDvMbMOXDLMfGO/ikuGfY+ZdfgNgNd9pJG0IecAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /></p>",
      "OPT1": "13",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "KKCqh8Ba1uin+55phdKFDg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu5": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn Ridge Regression, what does the penalty term added to the cost function in ridge regression penalize?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Large coefficients",
      "OPT2": "Small coefficients",
      "OPT3": "Constant terms",
      "OPT4": "Residuals",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu6": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a linear regression model, if the observed value of y is 8 and the predicted value is 10, what is the residual?</p>",
      "OPT1": "-2",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Mia2BqASzr4NzpQrQVinDA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu7": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn Lasso Regression, what does the penalty term added to the cost function encourage?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Sparse coefficients",
      "OPT2": "Large coefficients",
      "OPT3": "Small coefficients",
      "OPT4": "Constant terms",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu8": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tConsider a decision tree with 5 levels and 32 leaves. How many nodes does it have?</p>",
      "OPT1": "32",
      "OPT2": "64",
      "OPT3": "63",
      "OPT4": "31",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu9": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of following statements is/are correct?<br />\r\n\t<em>S</em><sub>1</sub> : Linear support vector machine is a parametric algorithm.<br />\r\n\t<em>S</em><sub>2</sub> : KNN is a non-parametric algorithm.</p>",
      "OPT1": "<p>\r\n\tOnly <em>S</em><sub>1</sub></p>",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\tOnly <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "OPT3": "<p>\r\n\tBoth <em>S</em><sub>1</sub> and <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "OPT4": "None of these",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu10": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a linear regression model with 50 observations and 2 predictor variables, if the confidence level for a confidence interval is 95%, what is the degrees of freedom for the t-distribution?</p>",
      "OPT1": "47",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "X0bvq3yMMWENvlvECRCuuw==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu11": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following is the correct way to preprocess the data for performing classification and regression?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Normalize the data \u2192 PCA \u2192 training",
      "OPT2": "PCA \u2192 normalize PCA output \u2192 training",
      "OPT3": "Normalize the data \u2192 PCA \u2192 normalize PCA output \u2192 training",
      "OPT4": "None of the above",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu12": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a linear regression model, if the Total Sum of Squares (TSS) is 100 and the Residual Sum of Squares (RSS) is 20, what is the coefficient of determination (<em>R</em><sup>2</sup>)?</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.8",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "XpkLAjvsL1tTT1pnw3P6Nw==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu13": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following statements regarding bias and variance are true?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Models which overfit have a high bias and underfit have a high variance.",
      "OPT2": "Models which overfit have a high bias and underfit have a low variance.",
      "OPT3": "Models which overfit have a low bias and underfit have a high variance.",
      "OPT4": "Models which overfit have a low bias and underfit have a low variance.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu14": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a decision tree, if a node has 6 possible outcomes with probabilities 0.1, 0.2, 0.1, 0.2, 0.2 and 0.2.<br />\r\n\tWhat is its Gini index?</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.16",
      "OPT2": "0.20",
      "OPT3": "0.82",
      "OPT4": "1",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu15": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tHow, can one address the bias-variance tradeoff in practice to enhance model performance?</p>",
      "OPT1": "By increasing the complexity of the model.",
      "OPT2": "By decreasing the complexity of the model.",
      "OPT3": "By collecting more training data.",
      "OPT4": "By using a more complex optimization algorithm.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu16": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of following statements is/are correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Large K value implies less bias for K cross-validation.",
      "OPT2": "Large K-value implies more bias for K cross-validation.",
      "OPT3": "Smaller K-value implies less variance for K cross-validation.",
      "OPT4": "Large K-value implies more variance for K cross-validation.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu17": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a decision tree, if a node has 3 possible outcomes with probabilities 0.4, 0.3 and 0.3 what is the entropy? (Rounded up to 2 decimal)</p>",
      "OPT1": "1.57",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "X4YoiuxZ/vk9kx4V7Xnk0A==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "TEST_NAME": "Discovered Test 6464880",
  "TEST_ID_ENCODED": "NjQ2NDg4MA==",
  "TEST_ID": "NjQ2NDg4MA=="
}